Hello Hello Friends, I had put the shampoo target
between September 1950, let's chart the fast
session, the morning open of September was 7040,
see its given 600 800, write it in the
chart, see this, it has already been
made upwards, that is our target at 723 and
see this from the daily war, so
see here, after making one, see
after 723 there has been a little profit booking,
after profit booking, see this the
closing price is
setting at that level at 704 after a slight movement, so
friends, see here, I
believe that a Boss Pack can come
because it was made from this, now
06 has to be created in 724, so there were
full chances of doing so here, hence the first
target should be 722, this was the high and the
oil of September will dry fruits, due to which
you can see the label further above,
keep this in mind